Guide to the University Governance Records RG 3
Western Connecticut State University Archives and Special Collections
University Governance Records
1941-2016
Western Connecticut State University Archives and Special Collections
Western Connecticut State University. University Senate.
RG 3
151
18.75 Linear Feet, 17 boxes
The records in this collection contain materials regarding agreements between the University and: the Administrative and Residual Employee Union, Local 4200; American Association of University Professors; New England Regional Student Services; the State Board of Education; and the American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees. It also includes materials regarding the Community Relations Program, Faculty Handbooks, and University Senate minutes.
Provenance
Adminstrative transfer.
Access Restrictions
Open for research without restrictions.
Historical/Biographical Note
The Univerity Senate exists by the will of the Faculty. It serves as a policy making body along side the University Administration and the University President, and the Student Government Association.
Scope and Content Note
The records in this collection are divided into 8 series: (1) Administrative and Residual Employee Union, Local 4200, (2) American Association of University Professors, (3) American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, (4) Community Relations Program, (5) Faculty Handbooks, (6) New England Regional Student Services, (7) State Board of Education, and (8) University Senate. The University Senate Series is arranged into 6 sub-series: (1) Senate Meetings; (2) Senate Committees; (3) Senate Nofitications; (4) Requests for Approval; (5) Resolutions; (6) President's Files
The bulk of the record group spans 1941-2016 and documents the operations of Western Connecticut State University's Faculty Senate and its committees. The collection is organized by academic year and includes agendas, minutes, correspondence, by-laws, newsletters, membership lists, reports and resolutions, and voting records. Committee Reports are filed separately but are also interfiled within the minutes for a given academic year.
Researchers should also see the Truman A. Warner Papers, Western Connecticut State University History, for additional information concerning the University Senate.
Of special interest are the Curriculum Study papers for 1941-1947, which are representative of projects undertaken during President Ralph C. Jenkins tenure. Some of the documents are written by Jenkins and some by faculty, but all represent the spirit of his time here.
Series: 1; Administrative and Residual Employee Union, Local 4200, 1990-1999; Box 1; Arranged in alphabetical and chronological order.; Contracts.
Series: 2; American Association of University Professors (AAUP), 1970-2006; Box 1 and oversized 1.; Arranged in alphabetical and chronological order; Collective Bargaining Agreements, correspondence, council meeting minutes, and newsletters.
Series: 3; American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), 1975-1997; Box 1; Arranged in alphabetical and chronological order.; Constitution and Collective Bargaining Agreements.
Series: 4; Community Relations Program; An Action Study, 1968-1969; Box 1; Action Study.
Series: 5; Faculty Handbook, 1970-2006; Box 2; Arranged in chronological order.; Handbooks.
Series: 6; New England Regional Student Services (NEBHE), 1984-1987; Box 2; Arranged in alphabetical and chronological order.; Reports.
Series: 7; State Board of Education, 1945-1989; Box 3; Arranged in alphabetical and chronological order.; Reports, master plans, rules and regulations.
Series: 8; University Senate, 1941-2016; Boxes 3-13, Audio Recordings boxes 1 and 2; Arranged in chronological order within each sub-series.; (1)Senate Minutes: contains University Senate Minutes and supplemental materials; (2) Senate Committees: contains minutes, reports and other materials generated by University Senate sub-committees; (3) Senate Notifications: containe notification of senate actions; (4) Requests for Approval: contains University Senate requests for approval of Senate Resolutions from the University President; (5) Resolutions: containts both proposed and accepted resolutions by the University Senate; (6) President's Files: contains correspondence, notes, and related materials.
Series: 9: University Planning and Budget Committee: materials, 1995-2004; Arranged in alphabetical and chronological order.; contains planning and assessment materials.
Arrangement
Folders are arranged chronologically in each series.
The files are grouped into 8 series:
Missing Title
Administrative and Residual Employee Union
American Association of University Professors (AAUP), 1970-2006
American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), 1975-1997
Community Relations Program; An Action Study, 1968-1969
Faculty Handbook, 1970-2006
New England Regional Student Services (NEBHE), 1984-1987
State Board of Education, 1945-1989
University Senate, 1941-2016
University Planning and Budget Committee, 1994-2005
Related Material
Truman Warner Papers (for Senate materials from the 1960s and 1970s)
Student Government Association Records.
Separated Material
Digital versions of Senate minutes available at: http://www.wcsu.edu/senate/Senate%20archives.htm
Universities and colleges -- Administration.; Correspondence.; Audiotapes.; Minutes.; Western Connecticut State University, Faculty Handbook.; Publications.; Handbooks.; Community Relations Program.; American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME).; American Association of University Professors (AAUP).; Administrative and Residual Employee Union, Local 4200.; Connecticut State Board of Education.; New England Regional Student Services (NEBHE).; Rosenberg, Edwin.; Western Connecticut State University. University Senate.
- Series 1. Administrative and Residual Employee Union, Local 4200, 43037
  - Collective Bargaining Contract, Unit [P-5], 1990-1993; 43039 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Collective Bargaining Contract, Unit [P-5], 1994-1999; 43038 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Series 2. American Association of University Professors (AAUP), 43016
  - Annual Reports, 1976-1982; 43036 (Box 1, Folder 3-5)
  - Annual Reports, 1984-1989; 43035 (Box 1, Folder 6-7)
  - Annual Reports, 2005-2006; 43034 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Arbitration between CSU Board of Trustees and CSU-AAUP, In the Interest, 1993-1994; 43033 (Box 1, Folder 9-11)
  - C ollective Bargaining Agreement, 1977-2006; 43032 (Box 1, Folder 12-20)
  - Collective Bargaining Agreement, 2006; 43031 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Collective Bargaining for College & University Faculty, A Primer on, 1975; 43030 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, 1970-2005; 43029 (Box 1, Folder 23-24)
  - Council Meeting, Minutes of the, 1976-1978; 43028 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Collective Bargaining Newsletter, 1987-1988; 43027 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - CSU Newsletter, 1990-2004; 43026 (Box 1, Folder 27-28)
  - CSU Union News, 2004; 43025 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - FACT (Faculty Action/CT), 1980-1986; 43024 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Footnotes, 2003-2004; 43023 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Public Affairs Bulletin, 1979-1985; 43022 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Vanguard, 1979-1993; 43021 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Vanguard, 1994-1999, 2000-2006; 43020 (Box OS 1, Folder *)
  - WCSU NEWSLETTER, 1975-1996; 43019 (Box 1, Folder 34-39)
  - WCSU Western Union, 2001; 43018 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - This is CSU-AAUP, 1987-1991; 43017 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Series 3. American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), 43012
  - Ballot, 1993; 43015 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Constitution, 1975; 43014 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Collective Bargaining Agreement, 1977-1997, 2006; 43013 (Box 1, Folder 44-48)
- Series 4. Community Relations Program, 43010
  - Collective Bargaining Agreement, Action Study, 1968-1969; 43011 (Box 1, Folder 49-52)
- Series 5. Faculty Handbook, 42985
  - Misc. pages, 1970-1975; 43009 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - January 1973, Revised, 43008 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - August 1977, Revised, 43007 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - August 1977, Revised (c.2), 43006 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - (Part II, Temporary Insert for 1978-79 Academic Year), 1978-1979; 43005 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Fall 1980, Revised, 43004 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Handbook, 1983-1985; 43003 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Handbook, 1986-1988; 43002 (Box 2, Folder 8-9)
  - Faculty Handbook; Supplement, 1986-1988; 43001 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Handbook; c2, 1986-1988; 43000 (Box 2, Folder 11-12)
  - Faculty Handbook, 1988-1993; 42999 (Box 2, Folder 13-15)
  - Faculty Handbook;, Supplements Nos. 1-3, 1988-1993; 42998 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Faculty Handbook; c2, 1988-1993; 42997 (Box 2, Folder 17-19)
  - Faculty Handbook, 1993-1998; 42996 (Box 2, Folder 20-21)
  - Faculty Handbook; Supplements 1-2, 1993-1998; 42995 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Faculty Handbook, 1993-1998; 42994 (Box 2, Folder 23-24)
  - Faculty Handbook; c2, 1996-2001; 42993 (Box 2, Folder 25-27)
  - Faculty Handbook; Supplements 1-4, 1996-2001; 42992 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Faculty Handbook; c2, 1996-2001; 42991 (Box 2, Folder 29-30)
  - Faculty Handbook, 2001-2005; 42990 (Box 2, Folder 31-32)
  - Faculty Handbook; Supplement 1, 2001-2005; 42989 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Faculty Handbook; Supplement III, 2001-2005; 42988 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Adjunct Faculty Handbook, 2003-2004; 50466 (Box 2, Folder 34.1)
  - Adjunct Faculty Handbook, 2004-2005; 42987 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Adjunct Faculty Handbook, 2005-2006; 42986 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Series 6. New England Regional Student Services (NEBHE), 42982
  - Economic Competitiveness and International Knowledge, Staff Paper II, 1987; 42984 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - New England Regional Student Services, Enrollment Report, 1984-1985; 42983 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Series 7. State Board of Education, 42970
  - A Strategic Telecommunications Plan, 1989; 42981 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Data Acquisition Plan, 1986-87, 42980 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Financial Aids for Connecticut Students, Rev. 1970, 42979 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - HOPE...for Conn's Disadvantaged Children, Bulletin No.98, 1966; 42978 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Master Plan for Higher Education in Connecticut, Preliminary Draft, 1974-1979., 1973; 42977 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Master Plan for Higher Education in Connecticut, Preliminary Draft, 1974-1979., 42976 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Master Plan for Higher Education in Connecticut, Draft, First Biennial F43 Supplement, 1974; 42975 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Proposed Certification Rules and Regulations for Public School Personnel In Connecticut, To Supplant Connecticut School, undated; 42974 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Provision for the Physically Disabled, Doc.75-F-55 c-017, 75-M-80-017, 1975; 42973 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - State Curriculum Committee, Minutes, April 12, 1945; 42972 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Teacher Education, An Urgent Matter, by The Academy for Educational Development, Inc., 1966; 42971 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Series 8. University Senate, 42820
  - Senate Meetings
    - Senate Minutes and Supporting Materials, 1956-1958; 42900 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Senate Minutes and Supporting Materials, 1963-1966; 42899 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Senate Minutes and Supporting Materials, 1967-1968; 42898 (Box 6, Folder 41-42)
    - Senate Minutes and Supporting Materials, 1968-1969; 42897 (Box 6, Folder 43-45)
    - Senate Minutes and Supporting Materials, 1969-1970; 42896 (Box 6, Folder 46-48)
    - Senate Minutes and Supporting Materials, 1970-1971; 42895 (Box 6, Folder 49-50)
    - Senate Minutes and Supporting Materials, 1971-1972; 42894 (Box 6, Folder 51-53)
    - Senate Minutes and Supporting Materials, 1972-1973; 42893 (Box 7, Folder 1-3)
    - Senate Minutes and Supporting Materials, 1973-1974; 42892 (Box 7, Folder 4-6)
    - Senate Minutes and Supporting Materials, 1974-1975; 42891 (Box 7, Folder 7-8)
    - Senate Minutes and Supporting Materials, 1975-1976; 42890 (Box 7, Folder 9-10)
    - Senate Minutes and Supporting Materials, 1976-1977; 42889 (Box 7, Folder 11-13)
    - Senate Minutes and Supporting Materials, 1977-1978; 42888 (Box 7, Folder 14-17)
    - Senate Minutes and Supporting Materials, 1978-1979; 42887 (Box 7, Folder 18-19)
    - Senate Minutes and Supporting Materials, 1979-1980; 42886 (Box 7, Folder 20-21)
    - Senate Minutes and Supporting Materials, 1980-1981; 42885 (Box 7, Folder 22-26)
    - Senate Minutes and Supporting Materials, 1981-1982; 42884 (Box 7, Folder 27-30)
    - Senate Minutes and Supporting Materials, 1982-1983; 42883 (Box 7, Folder 31-34)
    - Senate Minutes and Supporting Materials, 1983-1984; 42882 (Box 7, Folder 35-38)
    - Senate Minutes and Supporting Materials, 1984-1985; 42881 (Box 7, Folder 39-41)
    - Senate Minutes and Supporting Materials, 1985-1986; 42880 (Box 7, Folder 42-45)
    - Senate Minutes and Supporting Materials, 1986-1987; 42879 (Box 8, Folder 1-4)
    - Senate Minutes and Supporting Materials, 1987-1988; 42878 (Box 8, Folder 5-8)
    - Senate Minutes and Supporting Materials, 1988-1989; 42877 (Box 8, Folder 9-16)
    - Senate Minutes and Supporting Materials, 1989-1990; 42876 (Box 8, Folder 17-30)
    - Senate Minutes and Supporting Materials, 1990-1991; 42875 (Box 8, Folder 31-45)
    - Senate Minutes and Supporting Materials, 1990-1991; 42874 (Box 9, Folder 1-4)
    - Senate Minutes and Supporting Materials, 1991-1992; 42873 (Box 9, Folder 5-9)
    - Senate Minutes and Supporting Materials, 1992-1993; 42872 (Box 9, Folder 10-14)
    - Senate Minutes and Supporting Materials, 1993-1994; 42871 (Box 9, Folder 15-18)
    - Senate Minutes and Supporting Materials, 1994-1995; 42870 (Box 9, Folder 19-23)
    - Senate Minutes and Supporting Materials, 1995-1996; 42869 (Box 9, Folder 24-28)
    - Senate Minutes, Policy and Budget Committee, 1995-1996; 42868 (Box 9, Folder 29-33)
    - Senate Minutes and Supporting Materials (c.2), 1995-1996; 42867 (Box 9, Folder 34-38)
    - Senate Minutes: includes committee minutes, 1996-1997; 42866 (Box 9, Folder 39-42)
    - Senate Minutes and Supporting Materials, 1997-1998; 42865 (Box 10, Folder 1-5)
      General
      First folder of group contains Senate minutes
    - Senate Minutes and Supporting Materials, 1998-1999; 42864 (Box 10, Folder 6-11)
    - Senate Minutes: includes Committee Minutes and Annual Reports, 1999-2000; 42863 (Box 10, Folder 12-15)
      First folder of group contains Senate minutes.
    - Senate Minutes, Audio Recordings Sep 15, 1999 - Apr 18, 2001, 1999-2001; 42862 (Box 1)
    - Audio Recordings of Senate Meetings, 1999-2001; 49849 (Box Tape 1, Item 1-36, Box Tape 2, Item 37-38)
      38 audiocassetts and one DAT.
    - Senate Minutes and Supporting Materials, 2000-2001; 42860 (Box 10, Folder 16-24)
    - Senate Minutes, Audio Recordings May 16, 2001, 42861 (Box 1)
    - Senate Minutes and Committee Reports, 2002; 42859 (Box 10, Folder 25-28)
    - Senate Minutes and Supporting Materials, 2003; 50779 (Box 10, Folder 29-31)
    - Senate Minutes and Supporting Materials, 2004; 50780 (Box 10, Folder 32-34)
    - Senate Meeting Minutes and Supporting Materials September, 2004; 42848 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      General note
      2008 Accretion
    - Senate Meeting Minutes and Supporting Materials October, 2004; 42847 (Box 11, Folder 8-9)
    - Senate Meeting Minutes and Supporting Materials November, 2004; 42845 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Senate Meeting Minute and Supporting Materials December, 2004; 42844 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Senate Meeting Minutes and Supporting Materials, 2005; 42843 (Box 11, Folder 12-13.1)
    - Senate Meeting Minutes and Supporting Materials, 2006; 42841 (Box 13, Folder 31-32)
    - Senate Meeting Minutes and Supporting Materials, 2007 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Senate Committees
    - Curriculum Committee Study, 1941-1947; 42968 (Box 3, Folder 12-15)
    - Curriculum Committee Reports, 10/41-4/45 (w/gaps), 1941-1945; 42967 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - New Science Building Committee Minutes, 1950; 42901 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Curriculum Committee; Reports, 6/50-6/52 (w/gaps), 1950-1952; 42966 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Curriculum Committee; Minutes, 3/53-12/53, 1953; 42965 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Curriculum Committee; Minutes and Reports, 1/54-12/54, 1954; 42964 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Four-College Graduate Comm. Minutes, 1955-1960; 42902 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Curriculum Committee; Minutes, 1/56-11/56, 1956; 42963 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Curriculum Committee; Minutes, 2/57-12/57, 1957; 42962 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Curriculum Committee; Minutes, 1/58-12/58, 1958; 42961 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Curriculum Committee; Faculty Workshop, 5/58-6/58, 1958; 42960 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Curriculum Committee; Minutes, 1/59-8/59 (w/gaps), 1959; 42959 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Curriculum Committee; Liberal Arts Curriculum, 10/60-10/62, 1960-1962; 42958 (Box 3, Folder 25-26)
    - Curriculum Committee; Minutes, 6/60-8/62, 1960-1962; 42957 (Box 3, Folder 27-29)
    - Curriculum Committee; Minutes, 2/63-10/63, 1963; 42956 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Curriculum Committee; Minutes, 12/63-4/65, 1963-1965; 42955 (Box 3, Folder 31-32)
    - Curriculum Committee; Minutes, 10/64-5/65, 1964-1965; 42954 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Curriculum Committee; Minutes, 3/65-6/66, 1965-1966; 42953 (Box 3, Folder 34-35)
    - Curriculum Committee; Minutes, 10/66-5/67, 1966-1967; 42952 (Box 3, Folder 36- 37)
    - Curriculum Committee; Minutes, 6/67-9/68, 1967-1968; 42951 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Curriculum Committee; Minutes, 9/68-5/69, 1968-1969; 42950 (Box 3, Folder 39-40)
    - Curriculum Committee; Minutes, 9/69-5/70, 1969-1970; 42949 (Box 3, Folder 41-43)
    - Curriculum Committee; Minutes, 9/70-5/71, 1970-1971; 42948 (Box 3, Folder 44-48)
    - Curriculum Committee; Minutes, 9/71-5/72, 1971-1972; 42947 (Box 4, Folder 1-4)
    - Curriculum Committee; Minutes, 9/72-6/73, 1972-1973; 42946 (Box 4, Folder 5-9)
    - Curriculum Committee; Minutes, 9/73-5/74, 1973-1974; 42945 (Box 4, Folder 10-15)
    - Curriculum Committee; Minutes, 9/74-3/75, 1974-1975; 42944 (Box 4, Folder 16-19)
    - Curriculum Committee; Minutes, 2/75-5/75, 1975; 42943 (Box 4, Folder 20-23)
    - Curriculum Committee; Minutes, 9/75-2/76, 1975-1976; 42942 (Box 4, Folder 24-27)
    - Curriculum Committee; Minutes, March - May, 1976; 42941 (Box 4, Folder 28-31)
    - Curriculum Committee; Minutes, September 1976- May 1977, 1976-1977; 42940 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Curriculum Committee; Minutes, February 1977- October 1977, 42939 (Box 4, Folder 33-35)
    - Curriculum Committee; Minutes, September 1977- May 1978, 1977-1978; 42938 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Curriculum Committee; Review, December 1977- April 1978, 1977-1978; 42937 (Box 4, Folder 37-39)
    - Curriculum Committee; Administrative Review, April 1978- August 1978, 42936 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Curriculum Committee; Minutes September 1978- May 1979, 1978-1979; 42935 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Curriculum Committee; Approved Courses, October, 1978-1979; 42934 (Box 4, Folder 42-43)
    - Curriculum Committee; Course Descriptions & Approvals, January - April, 1979; 42933 (Box 4, Folder 44-45)
    - Curriculum Committee; Course Outlines & Approvals, 4/79-6/79, 1979; 42932 (Box 5, Folder 1-2)
    - Curriculum Committee; Admin. Review & Course Descriptions, 10/79-1/80, 1979-1980; 42931 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Curriculum Committee; Admin. Review of Comm. Actions, 12/79-2/80, 1979-1980; 42930 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Curriculum Committee; Admin. Review (Catalog Deadline), 2/80-4/80, 1980; 42929 (Box 5, Folder 5-7)
    - Curriculum Committee; Admin. Review, 2/80-6/80, 1980; 42928 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Curriculum Committee; Admin. Review, 10/80-12/80, 1980; 42927 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Curriculum Committee; Admin. Review, 9/80-3/81, 1980-1981; 42926 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Curriculum Committee; CWCC Report, 10/80-4/81, 1980-1981; 42925 (Box 5, Folder 11-12)
    - Curriculum Committee; Actions & Approvals, 4/81-11/81, 1981; 42924 (Box 5, Folder 13-14)
    - Curriculum Committee; Admin. Approvals for Committee, 10/81-1/82, 1981-1982; 42923 (Box 5, Folder 15-16)
    - Curriculum Committee; Admin. Review & Course Approvals, 12/81-6/82, 1981-1982; 42922 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Curriculum Committee; Agenda & Minutes, 9/82-5/83, 1982-1983; 42921 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Curriculum Committee; Working Material, 3/82-3/83, 1982-1983; 42920 (Box 5, Folder 19-24)
    - Curriculum Committee; Annual Report & Course Approvals, 10/82-6/83, 1982-1983; 42919 (Box 5, Folder 25-26)
    - Academic Leave Committee, 1984; 42854 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Curriculum Committee; Minutes & Course approvals, 9/83-2/84, 1983-1984; 42918 (Box 5, Folder 27-29)
    - Curriculum Committee; Annual Report & Course Approvals, 1/84-7/84, 1984; 42917 (Box 5, Folder 30-33)
    - Curriculum Committee; Minutes, 9/84-8/85, 1984-1985; 42916 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Curriculum Committee; Course Proposals & Approvals, 4/84-6/85, 1984-1985; 42915 (Box 5, Folder 35-40)
    - Curriculum Committee; Minutes and Agenda, 10/85-1/86, 1985-1986; 42914 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Curriculum Committee; Course Proposals & Approvals, 10/85-11/86, 1985-1986; 42913 (Box 5, Folder 42-47)
    - Curriculum Committee; Course Proposals & Approvals, 11/85-6/86, 1985-1986; 42912 (Box 6, Folder 1-5)
    - Curriculum Committee; Minutes, 9/86-1/87, 1986-1987; 42911 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Curriculum Committee; Course Proposals & Approvals, 9/86-1/87, 1986-1987; 42910 (Box 6, Folder 7-9)
    - Curriculum Committee; Minutes, 1/87-7/87, 1987; 42909 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Curriculum Committee; Course approvals, July 1987, 42908 (Box 6, Folder 11-14)
    - Curriculum Committee; Minutes & Course Approvals, 9/87 - 1/88, 1987-1988; 42907 (Box 6, Folder 15-18)
    - Curriculum Committee; Minutes & Course Approvals, 1/88 - 7/88, 1988; 42906 (Box 6, Folder 19-23)
    - Curriculum Committee; Minutes & Course Approvals, 9/88 - 11/88, 1988; 42905 (Box 6, Folder 24-25)
    - Curriculum Committee; Minutes & Course Approvals, 11/88 - 7/89, 1988-1989; 42904 (Box 6, Folder 26-31)
    - Curriculum Committee; Minutes & Course Approvals, 9/89 - 1/90, 1989-1990; 42903 (Box 6, Folder 32-36)
    - Academic Leave Committee and Reports, 1991-1999; 42853 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Academic Leave Committee, 2000-2002; 42852 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - International Center Minutes, 2004; 42833 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Center for Collaboration Minutes, 2004; 42832 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - CUCAS Minutes, 2004-2005; 42838 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - EAP Committee Minutes, 2004-2005; 42837 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Graduate Council Minutes, 2004-2005; 42836 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Graduate Council Minutes, 2004-2005; 42825 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Research & Development Committee Minutes, 2004-2005; 42835 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Academic Leave Reports, 2005; 42851 (Box 11, Folder 4-5)
    - Academic Leave Committee, 2006; 42849 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Tenure, Promotion & Terminal Degrees Program, Dec. 18, 2006; 42856 (Box 10a, Folder 2)
  - Senate Notifications
    - Notification of Senate Action, 2014 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Notification of Senate Action, 2015 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Notification of Senate Action February, 2016 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Notification of Senate Action March, 2016 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Notification of Senate Action April, 2016 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Notification of Senate Action May, 2016 (Box 13, Folder 6-7)
    - Notification of Senate Action, Sep 2017- Dec 2017 (Box 13, Folder 7.1)
  - Requests for Approval
    - Requests for Administrative approval with no Resolution numbers, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 30)
      Requests for approval:
      To amend the bylaws of the Individual Admissions Program as recommended by the IAP Committee.
      Approval of the Bylaws and recommendation to the President that the Institute for Holistic Health Studies be established.